https://www.rmu.edu/privacy

Skip to main content
Privacy Policy
Information Collection and Use
Robert Morris University (RMU) collects personally identifiable information when users submit forms (for example, applications for admittance or requests for information and services) on the Website.
Personally identifiable information includes any information that could reasonably be used to identify the user. This includes name, address, e-mail address, Social Security number, birth date, bank account information, credit card information, or any combination of information that could be used for identification purposes.
Forms collect only that information that is necessary to fulfill users' requests.
RMU uses this information to support the administrative needs of the University in areas such as admissions, financial aid, registration and communications.
Cookies
Robert Morris University utilizes monitoring and reporting services from Google and other partners to analyze website usage trends. These services use cookie-based tracking to provide this information. RMU also uses cookies to log session information and balance visitors across various web-site resources. You can read more about Google’s policies, procedures and opt-out opportunities and learn how-to opt out of any third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting www.networkadvertising.org/choices/.
Website Activity and Logs
Robert Morris University collects server and security logs containing basic information about visits to our websites. The following information is typical of what may be collected and stored automatically from all website visitors: Internet protocol (IP) address, web page(s) requested, referring web page, date and time, and the type of web browser being used. This data may be acquired, stored and analyzed for the purposes of improving the content of the website, analyzing trends, investigating security concerns, and improving services. This information is not reported or used in any manner that would reveal personally identifiable information, and will not be released to outside (third) parties unless legally required.
Information Sharing and Disclosure
RMU provides limited information to University vendors as necessary to provide contractual services. Information collected on the RMU Website will not be sold or publicly distributed. Robert Morris University complies with the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA) regulations.
Ensuring Accuracy of Information
The RMU website provides a system to view and/or update certain personally identifiable information. Authorized users can update or correct their mailing addresses and phone numbers.
Protecting Information/Security
RMU provides measures to protect information as it passes across the Internet using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology, which encrypts the transmission of information that users submit. Detailed account information is password-protected for privacy and security. Only authorized users may access account information.
E-mail Communication
RMU uses e-mail to send University news and information. A number of forms on the Website utilize e-mail to facilitate requests. E-mail communications are not encrypted, so the University advises caution when including private, sensitive information.
Contacting the Website
If you have any questions about this Website Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Website, contact the Office of Information Technology & Services at TheSentry@rmu.edu.
Sidebar Menu - Legal & Misc.
Research and Innovation in Simulation Education (RISE)
Who was Robert Morris?
Veterans Integration to Academic Leadership (VITAL)
